你們等一下
Hey, you guys.
我打包了一些碗碟給你們在新房子用
I packed up some dishes for the new house.
我甚至還找到了你的舊鴨嘴杯
I even found your old sippy cup
給小不點出生以后用
for when the little one comes along.
-真好 -謝謝 鄧菲先生
- Aww. - Thanks, Mr. D.
謝謝爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
媽媽還是黑著臉嗎
Is, uh, Mom still in there making that judgy face?
海莉 你都認識她二十五年了
Haley, you've known her for 25 years.
黑臉是她的預設表情
Just call it her face.
海莉的懷孕初期并不順利
Haley's pregnancy is off to a rough start.
惡心反胃 情緒無常 失眠...
Nausea, moodiness, trouble sleeping...
這些癥狀克萊爾都有
Claire's got it all.
至于我 我只想保持
Me, I'm just trying to keep the peace
激素水平穩定
here in Hormone Town.
你能相信嗎 克萊爾
Oh, can you believe it, Claire?
我們的小女孩長大了
Our little girl is growing up.
是啊 她被逮捕并被大學開除后
Yeah, it seems like just yesterday
我們把這些箱子搬到樓下
we were carrying all these boxes downstairs
仿佛就發生在昨天
after she got arrested and kicked out of college.
是啊 我也經歷了很多
Yeah, I've been through a lot, too.
我當過加長禮車司機 當過主唱
I've been a limo driver, a lead singer,
當過牧場工人 還有迪士尼樂園的唱歌紳士
a ranch hand, a Dapper Dan at Disneyland,
T恤設計師 標志牌旋舞者
a t-shirt designer, a sign spinner
現在是個即將迎來小寶寶的護理專業學生
and now a nursing student with a baby on the way.
一切都按計劃進行
It's all going according to plan.
所以我們想拿點東西過去
Oh. So, we're gonna take some stuff over.
等下等下等下 我們來
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Let's get a, uh --
我們來拍個母女合照
Let's get a mother/daughter picture.
親愛的 我不
Oh... Oh, honey, I don't --
我們 我們真的沒必要這樣
we -- we really don't have to.
別啊 會很棒的
No, no, no. It'll be cute.
爸爸 你太奇怪了 沒人想要這樣
Uh, Dad, you're being weird. No one wants this.
保持姿勢
Hang on here.
不對 這是我的指頭
Nope, that's my finger.
有好多有趣的濾鏡
So many fun filters.
趕緊拍吧
Just take the picture!
克萊爾 想得陽光一些
Claire, look at the positive.
我們的孩子之一終于搬走了
One of our kids is finally moving out.
她驗孕之后我就再也不想聽到"陽"字了
After her pregnancy test, I've had enough positives.
有點提醒我另外兩個孩子還沒有結婚生子
Kind of reminds me of two other unmarried, pregnant,
上次看到熱戀情侶搬到一起是在...
lovestruck kids who moved in together about...
大概二十五年前吧
25 years ago.
那不一樣
It's not the same.
是嗎 酸洗他們的牛仔褲
I don't know. Acid-wash their jeans
再往迪蘭的耳朵上掛捕夢網
and put a dream catcher in Dylan's ear,
就簡直是翻版了
and it's exactly the same.
親愛的 我昨晚做了個夢
Honey, I had a dream last night
他們把寶寶忘在出租車上
that they left the baby in an Uber,
我不得不縮小自己
and I had to shrink myself down
征用一只蜂鳥去找寶寶
to commandeer a hummingbird to find it.
不是你又跟知名主播的春夢我就很慶幸了
I'm just glad it wasn't another Jake Tapper sex dream.
我很焦慮 我害怕他們能力不足...
I'm mad. I'm scared they're in over their heads --
克萊爾 已經發生了 他們要有寶寶了
Claire, it's happening. They're having the baby.
列車都離站了 你就上車吧
The train's left the station. Get on board.
行吧
Fine.
你說得對
You're right.
你是對的 我 我會試著積極一點的
You're right. I'll -- I'll try to be positive.
好極了 我正準備為他們挑件喬遷賀禮
Good. I was gonna go pick up a house-warming gift for them.
-和我一起吧 -行 走吧
- Why don't you come with me? - Oh, okay, let's do that.
等一下 你要怎么登上一輛
Wait a second. How do you board a train
已經離站的列車
that's already left the station?
不知道 也許你可以和那個主播一起
I don't know. Maybe you could catch up to them
乘著蜂鳥趕上他們
on a hummingbird with Jake Tapper.
你脫身了
Well, you're off the hook.
我要獨自飛往布蘭森
I'm flying to Branson solo,
我想我會坐在一個陌生人身旁
and I guess I'll be sitting next to a stranger
參加《奧斯蒙兄弟:向嘻哈致敬》
at The Osmond Brothers: A Tribute to Hip Hop.
他們來康普頓的時候我會抓住機會的
Well, I'll catch them when they come to Compton,
不過還是謝了
but thank you.
你為我姐姐小帕做了那么多
Well, it's the least I could do
這是我唯一能做的
after what you did for my sister, Pam.
我姐姐 小帕 要來接卡爾去...
My sister, Pam, is coming to pick up Cal to --
回到密蘇里
to take him back to Missouri.
她本來應該在監獄里再待三個月的
She was supposed to be in prison another three months,
但我了不起的丈夫
but my wonderful husband,
普里契特地檢官助理 寫了一封信
Assistant D.A. Pritchett, wrote a letter
呼吁提早釋放她
advocating for her early release.
這沒什么
It was nothing.
其實真的沒什么
It actually was nothing.
我從來沒寫過什么信
I never wrote any letter.
因為... 感覺就是不對的
It just -- It didn't feel right.
小帕毫無悔改之意 她的判決也很公正
Pam showed no remorse, and her sentence was fair.
然后出于某種原因
And -- And then for some reason,
但不管怎樣 他們決定讓她早點出獄
they decided to let her out early anyway.
很幸運 假釋記錄是密封的
Fortunately, uh, parole records are sealed,
所以小帕和小卡永遠也不會知道
so Pam and Cam will never know,
我也不用去布蘭森了
and I don't have to go to Branson
聽奧斯蒙兄弟叫觀眾喊個"啥啥"
and hear the Osmonds ask if they can get a "What-what."
是她
That's her!
卡爾 你媽媽來啦
Cal, that's your mom!
她剛結束了... 旅行
She's back from her, um...trip?
鐵窗之旅
Up the river.
小帕 她來啦
Pam! There she is!
-你們好啊 -見到你太高興了
- Hey, y'all! - Oh, it's so good to see you!
-嗨 -嗨 媽媽
- Hi! - Hi. Momma!
是我的小炸雞塊啊
There's my little chicken nugget!
我的老天
Ooh, my goodness!
我太想你了 你過得怎么樣
I missed you so much. How have you been?
他們每天晚上都給我讀故事
They read to me every night.
別擔心 寶寶
Aw, don't worry, baby.
不用再受那種折磨了
That's all over now.
差點忘了
Oh, almost forgot!
看看媽媽為你做了什么
Look what Momma made you.
我要把它放在我的自行車上
I'm gonna put it on my bike!
他要安在自己的自行車上
Oh, he's gonna put it on his bike!
小帕 真高興你出獄了
Oh, Pam, it is so great that you're out.
里面一定很孤單
It must've been so lonely in there.
還是有人陪的
Well, there was some companionship.
真好
Good.
-我嘗試了女同性戀 -好吧
- I dabbled in lesbianism. - Oh.
并不反感
Didn't hate it.
就是事后話太多
But there was just too much talking afterwards.
-好了 我去給你倒點冰茶 -好的
- Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna get you some iced tea. - Yeah.
還有 很抱歉你不能住在樓上
Again, I'm -- I'm so sorry that you can't stay upstairs.
-我們有新的租客要搬進來 -閉嘴吧
- We have this new renter coming in, and - Cram it.
我知道你根本沒寄那封信
I know you didn't send that letter.
什么 你怎么知道
What? H-How?
我怎么知道不重要
That don't matter.
重要的是你會付出代價的
All that matters is you're gonna pay.
在監獄里大家叫我肉毒桿菌
In prison, they called me BOTOX,
因為雖然所有女人都想要我[美容用]
because even though all the ladies want me,
我還是會弄爛你的臉
I will wreck your face.
雪莉 我不確定自己喜歡這身打扮
Sherry, I-I don't know if I like these.
褲子太短了
They're so short.
不啊 就是這種風格 寶貝
No, that's the style, boo.
我就是覺得自己的腳踝不太適合穿這個
I just don't know if I have the ankles for this.
對 這種褲子對拉丁人一點都不友好
Yeah, those pants are no good for Latin people.
穿上去像是要跑著趟水過河
They make you look like you're trying to run across a river.
我倒覺得你看起來很不錯
Well, I think you look great.
你應該以后只穿這種褲子
You should only wear pants like that from now on.
好的
Okay.
曼尼 我們該開始為你的生日派對
Manny, we should start sending invitations
寄邀請函了
for your birthday party.
是嗎 我以為我們要去
Oh, but I thought we were gonna go to
奧海鎮啞劇品酒節慶祝你的生日
the Ojai Mime and Wine Festival for your birthday?
對 我們還是不要辦派對了 媽
Oh, yeah, maybe we shouldn't do the party, Mom.
這太瘋狂了
This is crazy.
曼尼害怕啞劇
Manny's terrified of mimes.
而且他討厭中央山谷的葡萄酒
And he hates Central Valley wine.
好消息
Hey, great news.
我的當月香腸早到了一天
My Sausage of the Month arrived a day early.
你一定要在這見證開箱
You get to be here for the un-boxing.
這次我不錄像了
I'm not gonna film it this time.
波蘭熏腸 太好了
Kielbasa, yes!
他們又聽取了我的建議
They took my suggestion again.
我跟你說過那不是建議
I told you it's not a suggestion.
網頁上是讓你選一種口味
The web page is just asking you to choose one.
總之 我們有麻煩了
Anyways, we have a problem.
雪莉總是對曼尼發號施令
Sherry is bossing Manny around.
這太讓人難以接受了
Oof, that's a lot to take in.
你能用你的獨家醬料做一下香腸嗎
Can you cook these up with that special sauce you do?
你得去告訴他
You have to go and tell him
-他要站起來為自己說話 -為什么我去
- that he needs to stand up for himself. - Why me?
我覺得我們壓根就不應該干涉 但是
I-I don't think we should get involved at all, but, I mean,
如果你覺得有問題 那應該你去說
if it's a problem for you, then you do it,
因為我不在乎
'cause I don't care.
我不能去
I can't.
如果是我說曼尼女朋友的壞話
If I say something bad about Manny's girlfriend,
他是不會聽的 因為那樣我就成了
he's not gonna listen, because I am the mother
認為沒人配得上她小寶貝的那種媽媽
who thinks that nobody's good enough for her little boy.
-那就別插手了 -不行 因為她就是
- Just let it go. - I can't because she's not good enough
配不上我的小寶貝
for my little boy.
我還是不了
I'm gonna take a pass.
那我也不用我外婆的洋蔥辣醬
Then I'm gonna take a pass making your sausages
給你做香腸
with my grandmother's spicy onion sauce.
好吧 我去
Fine, I'll do it.
說好的原配才會要求一大堆呢
But all these demands don't sound very second wife-y.
孩子
Hey, kid.
我得跟你聊聊你和你女朋友
I need to talk to you about you and your girlfriend.
這話題可能有點敏感
It's a sensitive subject.
如果你想說昨天晚上從我房間傳出來的聲音
If this is about the sounds coming from my room last night,
那不是你想的那樣
it wasn't what you think.
我們是在重新布置家具
We were rearranging the furniture, and then
然后為成功改造而慶功
we were congratulating each other on how it turned out.
令人難過的是 我真的信你
Sadly, I believe you.
我以為你喜歡家具保持原樣
I thought you liked your furniture exactly like it was?
我們還因為這開除了兩個清潔女工
We fired two cleaning women over this.
我之前也以為 但是其實不是的
I thought I did, too, but it turns out I didn't.
其實我不想聊的正是這件事
Actually, that's what I don't want to talk to you about.
有沒有可能雪莉總是對你發號施令
Is it possible Sherry pushes you around?
你什么意思
What are you saying?
我不知道
I don't know.
就是男人一點
Be the man, you know.
有點骨氣
Show some backbone.
-這么說簡直太有你的風格了 -才沒有
- That is such a you thing to say. - It really isn't.
這樣看待男女關系太老套了
It's such an old way of looking at relationships.
性別角色不再重要了
Gender roles don't matter anymore.
這就是你穿她褲子的原因嗎
Is that why you're wearing her pants?
我來跟你講講 杰
Let me tell you something, Jay.
就像長腿褲
Just like long pants,
荼毒人心的男子氣概那一套已經落伍了
toxic machismo has gone out of style.
對對 你說的都對 男子氣概不好
Yeah. Yeah, masculinity's bad
但等需要男子氣概打死蜘蛛時就知道了
till someone has to kill a spider.
歡迎來到弗萊徹大街14 7/8號
Welcome to 14 7/8 Fletcher Ave.
真溫馨 是吧
Wow. This is cozy, huh?
這是車庫改裝的
Well, it's a converted garage,
所以是有點小
so I know it's a little bit small.
親愛的 只有用來住人才算小
Oh, honey, it's only small for a place to live.
我們給你們帶了個暖家禮物
Hey, we got you guys a housewarming gift.
是個菠蘿裝飾
It's a decorative pineapple
因為 菠蘿象征好運旺旺來
because, uh, pineapples are a symbol of good luck.
謝謝 鄧菲先生
Thanks, Mr. D.
這可比我們的大櫻桃好多了
That's way better than our giant cherry.
這是干凈馬桶的象征
That's just a symbol of a clean toilet.
謝謝老爸
Thanks, Dad.
不用客氣
You've very welcome.
這其實是我們倆一起的心意 對吧親愛的
It's actually from both of us, right, honey?
對對 因為我覺得
Right. Right, because I thought
你會需要很多好運
you would want a lot of luck.
媽媽 我知道你有何想法
Mom, look. I know what you're thinking...
但我們能省很多錢
...but we're saving a ton of money.
房租包水電費
Utilities are included,
我們不需要很多家具
we don't need a lot of furniture,
而且以后也不怕找不到寶寶了
and it'll be easy to keep track of the baby!
他們 他們還能步行到機場
And they can, uh -- they can walk to the airport.
然后又回到客廳
Which brings us back to the living room.
厲害 我們不用走動就看完你家了呢
Wow. We got the whole tour without even moving.
這年頭就流行小房子
Tiny-homes are very trendy these days.
對了 我也是這么
And, by the way, it's what I called
稱呼我高中的黑人矮子死黨
my short, black best friend in high school.
你們打算把嬰兒床放在哪
So, where -- where are you thinking of putting the baby's crib?
就放在這個天窗下面
We were thinking about putting it right there under the skylight.
這樣寶寶抬頭就能伸手摘天上的星星
That way, the baby can look up and reach for the stars.
我好喜歡這樣
Ohh, I love that.
而且你們看 那塊玻璃多干凈啊
And look how clean that glass is.
"干凈"得離奇了吧
A little too clean.
這不是天窗
It's -- It's not a skylight.
是你屋頂上有個洞
There's a hole in your roof.
真好 我一直想學如何安裝天窗
Cool, I always wanted to learn how to install a skylight.
擇日不如撞日了
I guess today's the day.
那你有沒有過把浴室里的插座
Have you also always wanted to move an electrical outlet
移到別處的想法呢
that's currently in the shower?
-這應該不是暗語吧 -不是的
- Well, that can't be code. - It's not.
我就是在說真實情況
I'm telling you exactly what's going on.
抱歉 我接個電話
Oh, excuse me.
海莉 乖女兒
Haley, honey.
你無法在這里養育寶寶
You can't raise a baby in here.
要是寶寶在哭
What happens if -- if the baby's crying
-但你要睡覺 怎么辦 -我想過了
- and you need to sleep? - Thought of it.
我們會掛起一張床單 隔出一個小房間
We're gonna put up a sheet to make it like a little room.
好機智
Oh, smart.
告訴我這哪里有用了
Tell me how this works.
哇哇哇 你能聽見我哭嗎
Wahh, wahh, wahh. Could you hear me?
我知道這里不理想 但我們沒問題的
I know it's not perfect, but we've got this.
我們比你想的要成熟多了
We're a lot more grown up than you think.
海莉 你能來廚房跟我談談嗎
Haley, can I talk to you for a second in the kitchen?
好
Yeah.
是醫生打來
Uh, that was the doctor.
我們這會兒應該到那里的
We're supposed to be there right now.
老天 超聲波 我忘得一干二凈了
Oh, my God. The ultrasound -- I totally spaced!
千萬不能讓我媽知道
We can't let my mom find out.
我們想個靠譜的借口 然后出門
Um, let's just make up something responsible and get out of here.
-好的 -好咧
- Okay. - Okay.
我們要出門買牙刷
So, we need to go and get toothbrushes.
你應該掛起床單的
You should've put up a sheet.
我們都聽見了
We heard everything.
你錯過了第一次超聲波預約嗎
You missed your first ultrasound appointment?
你再繼續教訓我 就真趕不上了
Well, we will if you keep lecturing me.
-醫生是誰 -我們從點評網上找到的
- Who's the doctor? - We found her on Yelp.
她有四星好評呢
She has, like, four stars.
害盧克肚子里長蟲那家壽司餐廳也有四星好評
So does the sushi place that gave Luke worms.
我跟你一起去
I'm coming with you.
那我就留在這
I think I'm just gonna hang back
完成安裝天窗的任務吧
and commence Operation Skylight.
我車停在后面了 我們從這邊走
I parked in back. Let's go this way.
老天
Oh, God!
真幸運 我們剛買了掃把
That is lucky! We just bought a broom.
這不是我最喜歡的大姑嘛
Hey, there's my favorite sister-in-law.
我給你買了根冰棒
I, uh -- I got you a Popsicle,
棍子上有個冷笑話
and the stick has a joke on it.
"如何修好壞掉的大猩猩"
Um, "How do you fix a broken gorilla?"
我想很快就知道答案了
Mm, well, I guess we're gonna find out soon.
棍子不止能用來寫冷笑話
Sticks are good for more than joking.
我在監獄里學會了如何把
In prison, I learned how to fashion
各式各樣的棍子磨成小刀
all manner of sticks into knives.
你在牢里還有時間做手工 好棒呀
You know, I love that you had time for crafts in there.
我還學會了 如果你不兌現自己所做的承諾
I also learned if you don't do what you say you're gonna,
就會被教訓
you get hurt.
我去看看小卡爾
Um, I'm gonna go, uh, check on Cal.
不不不 我去吧
No, no, no, I'll do it.
我想在你帶他回家前
I want to soak up as much time with him as I can
盡量多跟他在一起
before you take him home.
小卡爾
Cal.
小卡爾 那是什么 快放下
Cal, what is -- Put that down!
他從哪弄來的芝士漢堡
Where did he get a cheeseburger?
我不知道
I don't know.
聽我說 信的事我很抱歉
Hey, look. I'm -- I-I'm sorry about the letter,
但結果不是很好嗎
but it all worked out.
你還是提前獲釋了
You still got out early.
那僅僅是因為我自愿幫忙訓練警犬
Only because I volunteered to help train police dogs.
那經歷太可怕了
It was horrible.
我要偷電視機啦
I'm stealing a TV!
放開我
Get off of me!
怎么還會痛
I feel it!
你到底想要我怎么樣
What do you want from me?
-把里程給我 -什么
- Miles. - Uh, what?
我知道你們有錢人的信用卡積分能兌換里程
I know all you fancy people have rewards cards.
被關了那么久 我很想去旅行
Being all cooped up has given me the travel bug.
但我存了很久呢
But I've been saving those.
我有半年都去加油站買日用品
I bought groceries at a gas station for six months
就為了得到三倍積分
to get triple points.
我們給莉莉準備的生日早餐
For -- For Lily's birthday breakfast,
是山寨的夾心餅干
we gave her something called Pop Zarts.
今天之內
I want them in my account
把里程轉到我賬戶 否則我就告訴小卡
by the end of the day or I tell Cameron.
但我差不多能兌換兩張去巴黎的非熱門時段機票了
But I almost have enough for two off-peak flights to Paris.
"猴子扳手"[壞事精]
Ha, "Monkey wrench."
你還說得真輕巧
Yeah, that's putting it mildly.
不是 這是修好壞掉的大猩猩的方法 死蠢
No, that's how you fix a broken gorilla, you dummy.
你在這呢 進行得如何
Oh, there you are. How did it go?
不順利
Not well.
他惱羞成怒 說我是老古董
He got all mad, called me old-fashioned.
我 我可給艾麗克斯買了本
Me -- the guy who bought Alex a book
有關成功商業女士的書
on successful business ladies.
不好意思 我沒聽懂
Sorry, I didn't understand that.
請再說一遍
Please try again.
那個咖啡研磨機怎么老和我說話
Why does that coffee grinder keep talking to me?
你信守諾言
Well, you kept your end of the bargain,
所以我會給你做香腸
so I'm gonna make the sausages,
然后來討論下一步計劃吧
and we'll talk about the second step later.
沒有下一步 我已經去說過了
There's no second steps. I did it.
我不想再聽到這件事了
That's the last I want to hear about it.
真是"謝謝"你啊 杰
Thanks a lot, Jay.
我本應該忽視你的話
I should've ignored you,
但你的話影響了我
but you got in my head.
什么呀 我第一次聽到這事情呢
About what? This is first time I hear of this.
我開始想或許她真的對我有點頤指氣使
I started thinking maybe she does boss me around
所以我找她談了 談得有點過火
a little bit, so I confronted her, things got heated,
現在她叫了車要走了
and now she called a car and she's leaving.
我談過最棒的戀愛
The best relationship I've ever had,
估計要結束了
and I think it might be ending.
最后一次聽你的話了 杰
Last time I listen to you, Jay.
別擔心 寶貝 事情總會
Don't worry, papi. Those things have a way
-迎刃而解的 -算了 這還能怎么做呢
- of working themselves out. - Eh, what're ya gonna do?
是個好問題 你還能"怎么做"呢
Yeah, that's a good question. What are you going to do?
這樣不好
I'm calling it.
我不來了
I'm done.
正在給"布萊了""撥號"
Calling Brian Dunn.
別別別
No. No, no.
我欠他錢呢
I owe him money.
杰 你得去跟雪莉談談
Jay, you need to talk to Sherry
和她說這都是你的餿主意
and tell her that it was your idea.
我已經遵守約定了
I've kept up my part of the bargain.
你別跟我來哥倫比亞人那套
Now, don't go all Colombian
和我說如果我不和雪莉談
and tell me if I don't talk to Sherry
你就不做香腸
you're not making those sausages,
因為我已經吃了第二顆降膽固醇藥了
'cause I already took a second statin.
對不起 這次你得不到你想要的
Sorry, for once, you're not getting your way.
雪兒 有空嗎
Hey, Sher, got a sec?
不好說 司機巴特弗還有兩分鐘就到了
Uh, tough to say. Bartev is two minutes away,
但軟件顯示車在轉圈 所以...
but his car is spinning, so...
我知道你在生曼尼的氣
I know you're upset with Manny.
這都怪我
That's on me.
是我說了話影響了他的想法
I put some ideas in his head.
你知道 我對他來說就像個英雄
You know, I'm kind of a hero to him.
我沒想引起任何麻煩
I didn't mean to cause any trouble.
你知道 我很愛他
You know, I'm crazy about the kid,
我只是想確保他處于良好的戀愛關系之中
and I just want to make sure he's in a healthy relationship.
歌洛莉亞讓你這么做的 是不是
Gloria put you up to this, didn't she?
很復雜
It's complicated.
你看得出這有多諷刺吧
You do see the irony of this, right?
她擔心曼尼被人控制
She's so worried about Manny getting bossed around,
但她對你這樣就沒問題啦
yet she has no problem bossing you around?
-不不 不是這樣 -真的嗎
- No, no, that's crazy. - Really?
你本來是這么安排下午時光的嗎
Is this how you wanted to spend your afternoon?
不 我討厭這樣
No, I hate this.
我一整天都計劃好了
Man, I had a whole day planned.
聽著 我打算讓曼尼著急幾個小時
Listen, I'm gonna let Manny spiral for a few hours,
然后我們就上樓
and then we're gonna go back upstairs
"移家具"去
and move the furniture around.
天啊 居然真是"那檔事"
Oh, God, it was that.
但你需要為自己發聲
But you need to stand up for yourself.
你回去 告訴歌洛莉亞
You go back in there, and you tell Gloria
你受夠了對她唯唯諾諾
that you're tired of being told what to do.
-讓我想一下 -別想了
- Let me think about it. - Don't think.
-做就對了 -好
- Just do it. - Okay.
天啊
Oh! Oh.
放輕松 你有的我都看過
Relax. It's nothing I haven't seen before.
我以前可是在男子摔跤隊
I was on the boys' wrestling team.
你想要什么 我已經把里程給你了
What do you want? I transferred the miles.
我收到了 我決定了我不想旅行 但...
I got 'em. Decided I don't want to travel, though --
我把他們都換成禮品卡了
converted them all into gift cards.
不不不 他們說你不應該這么做
No, no, no, they say you're not supposed to do that.
我決定我想要點其他的
I decided I want something else.
我想搬到樓上
I want to move in upstairs,
我還想要一個高效空氣過濾器
and I want a HEPA air filter on account of I shed.
我跟你說過租出去了 我不能不讓人家來住
I told you it's rented. I can't just cancel on them.
你確定嗎
You sure about that?
因為我得不到我想要的
Because when I don't get what I want,
我就能讓事情變得"很難受"
I can make things real uncomfortable.
好冷 好冷
Oh, cold, cold!
怎么了
What's going on?
沒事
Nothing.
米奇爾和我聊天呢
Mitchell and I's just talking.
不不 我們沒 我不能
No, no, we weren't. I can't --
我不能再忍受了 對不起
I can't take this anymore. I'm sorry.
-我沒給假釋委員會寫信 -什么
- I never wrote the letter to the parole board. - What?
我想撒謊 但我做不到
I -- I tried to lie, but I just -- I couldn't do it.
但你對我撒謊卻沒問題啊
Yet you had no problem lying to me.
你就讓我姐姐待在可怕的監獄里受罪嗎
You just let my sister rot in that horrific hell hole?
得了吧 他們每周二都能吃玉米卷
Oh, please, they have a Taco Tuesday!
-小卡 我們能談下嗎 -等下
- Uh, Cam, c-can we talk? - Oh, hold up.
我在翻看一些
I'm just looking through some pictures of me
我幫你家人忙的照片
helping out your family.
這是我帶杰和歌洛莉亞去機場
Here I am taking Jay and Gloria to the airport,
這是我幫艾麗克斯搬到大學宿舍
and, oh, this is me, uh, helping Alex move into her dorm room,
誰能忘了菲爾的大變活人魔術
and who can forget when I helped Phil with that magic trick
我讓他把我變沒了
and let him make me disappear.
你沒在那個相片里
You're not in that picture.
這說明我幫忙很到位
That's how good I am at helping out.
現在我們來看看
Now let's take a look at some pictures
你幫我家人的照片吧
of you helping out my family.
小卡 我有嘗試寫信
Cam, I tried to write the letter.
我真的有 但她觸犯了法律
I -- I really did, but she broke the law,
她得到了公平的判決
and she got a fair sentence.
她不應該提前出獄
She did not deserve to get out early.
我真的撒不下這個謊
I-I couldn't bring myself to lie about it.
少來了你
Oh, give me a break.
我曾聽你親口說出
I have heard you say the words,
"頭發燙得真好看 曼尼"
"Nice perm, Manny."
你可以沒下限到那份上
You can get there.
我是法界人士
I am an officer of the law.
-我宣過誓 -那我們的誓言呢
- I took an oath. - What about our oath?
要愛彼此 尊重彼此
To love, honor, and --
為彼此的家人說謊
and lie for each other's family.
沒有那句
Oh, that's not part of it.
但暗含在內了
But it's implied.
住口 別吵了
Stop. Stop.
米奇爾說得對
Mitchell's right.
我一整天都在恐嚇他
I spent the day terrorizing him.
我是個糟糕的人
I'm a horrible person.
我不該這么早出獄
I should still be in jail.
看我偷了什么
Look what I took.
那是我的剃須刀嗎
Is that my beard trimmer?
也能剃其他地方的毛
Works on other hairs.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我偷 我騙 我操縱他人
I am a thief and a liar and a manipulator.
不能放任我這樣的人重返社會
I can't be trusted to rejoin society.
別這么說 你會沒事的
Hey, don't say that. You're-you're gonna be fine.
小卡爾怎么辦
What about little Cal?
他在這過得很好
He's doing so good here.
我只會毀了他
I'm just gonna ruin him.
我需要監管 需要重新被關起來
I need supervision, to be locked back up.
你們知道我能去哪弄輛皮卡
You guys know where I can get a pickup truck
和一根大鏈子嗎
and a big ol' chain?
我去偷個租碟亭回來
I'm gonna steal me a Redbox.
帕姆 你
Pam, hey, you...
你不必回監獄 明白嗎
You don't have to go back to prison, okay?
你可以住在樓上
You can stay upstairs.
你是真心的嗎
Do you mean it?
你們的租客怎么辦
What about your renters?
我們取消
We'll cancel, um,
我們會幫你照顧卡爾
and-and we'll help take care of Cal
直到你重新站穩腳跟 好嗎
until you can get back on your feet, okay?
家人是第一位的
Family first.
放在相冊里
One for the book.
我去樓上安頓一下 如果可以的話
I'm gonna go get settled upstairs. if it's okay,
我泡完澡再下來照顧卡爾
I'll come back down for Cal after my tub.
謝謝你們倆
Thank you both.
我不會忘記這份恩情的
I won't forget this.
你真善良
That was so sweet.
我很高興卡爾能留下來
I'm glad Cal gets to stick around.
現在小帕住在這
And now with Pam here,
我們去布蘭森時她可以幫忙喂貓
she can feed the cat while we go to Branson.
辛格醫生 您凝膠涂得絕妙
Dr. Singh, that is some exquisite gel work,
作為一名準護士
and I say that as a soon-to-be nurse
和用很多發"膠"的人 佩服
and someone who wears a lot of product in his hair.
謝謝
Thank you.
海莉 你有沒有服用產前維生素
Haley, have you been taking your prenatal vitamins?
我會確保她從現在起按時服用
I'll make sure she does from now on.
放松點 媽
Calm down, Mom.
每天吃一顆藥這種事我能記住
I can remember to take a pill every day.
真能記住嗎[避孕藥]
Can you?
聽到心跳了
There's the heartbeat.
聽起來好快 這正常嗎
Oh, it-it sounds so fast, is everything okay?
很正常 寶寶的心跳聽起來就該是這樣
No, that's good. That's the way a baby's heart should sound.
他說得對
He's right.
聽起來是一個非常健康...
It's the sound of a very healthy --
怎么了
What?
還有另一個心跳
There's a second heartbeat.
寶寶長了兩顆心嗎
A baby with two hearts?
我吃那塊大麻布朗尼時不知道自己懷孕了
I didn't know I was pregnant when I ate that brownie!
-我當時不知道 -海莉 深呼吸
- I didn't -- - No, H-Haley, breathe.
你懷了雙胞胎
You're having twins.
那不可能 你弄錯了
That's impossible. It's a mistake.
沒有弄錯 我很擅長我的工作
It's not. I'm pretty good at this.
她沒弄錯 在這能看到兩個寶寶
She's right. You can see them right here.
我不能生雙胞胎
I can't have twins.
我們準備好迎接一個寶寶 現在加倍了
That's twice as many babies as we were expecting.
是啊 我們會寡不敵眾的
Yeah, they'll outnumber us.
我們家里怎么住得下兩個寶寶
How are they gonna fit in our place?
我的身體怎么裝得下兩個寶寶
How are they gonna fit in my body?
永遠會有一個寶寶是醒的
One is always going to be awake.
我永遠別想睡了 雙胞胎嬰兒車那么寬
I'll never sleep again. And those double-strollers are so wide,
我再也不能進精品店買東西了
I can say goodbye to ever shopping in a boutique.
-海莉 不會有事的 -你又不知道
- Haley, everything's gonna be okay. - You don't know that.
-我知道 -我搞不定這些 媽
- I do! - I'm in way over my head, Mom, I --
但你不是一個人
But you're not alone.
是啊 還有我在
Yeah, I'll be here.
有他在 但我指的是我 有我在
Yeah, he'll be here, but I meant me. I'll be here.
可你最近沒怎么支持我
Yeah, but you kind of haven't been lately.
我知道
I know, I know,
我十分抱歉
and I'm very sorry about that,
但正如你很快就會發現的那樣
but as you're about to find out,
做媽媽十分復雜
being a mom is very complicated.
幸運的是 會激發很多母性本能
Luckily, there are these instincts that kick in,
特別是你的孩子遇到麻煩時
especially when your kid's in trouble.
所以假如你應顧不暇了
So if you're ever overwhelmed,
我就在你的肩頭
I am right over your shoulder
騎在蜂鳥的翅膀上
on the wings of a hummingbird.
這下我知道她的大麻布朗尼是從哪來的了
Now I know where she got the brownie.
我會在你身后一起騎蜂鳥 鄧太太
And I'll be right behind you on that hummingbird, Mrs. D.
這只蜂鳥只能一個人騎
It's kind of a hummingbird for one.
好了 曼尼和他女朋友沒事了
Okay, Manny and his girlfriend are good.
煮起來烤起來吧
Let's boil and broil.
謝謝你 杰 這就給你做兩根香腸
Thank you, Jay. Two sausages coming up.
兩根 當我是男團的小屁孩嗎
Two? What, am I in a boy band?
全做了
Make 'em all.
雪莉具體是怎么說的
So, what did Sherry say exactly?
沒說什么 你懂的 主要都是我發話
Not much. I, you know -- I did most of the talking.
希望她現在不會再對曼尼那么頤指氣使
Well, hopefully now she'll stop being so controlling.
是啊
Yeah.
不過其實挺好笑
Funny, though.
什么好笑
What is?
只是嘛... 你懂的
Well, it's just that, you know,
你很擔心曼尼妻管嚴
you were worried about Manny being pushed around,
但如果你反省一下
and if you think about it,
你也整天對我發號施令啊
you've been sort of pushing me around all day.
好笑的地方在哪
What's the funny part?
沒啊 只是...
No, it's just --
這想法從何而來
Where's this coming from?
沒有啊 我自己隨便想到的而已
Nothing, it's just something I thought of.
少來 你才不想事情
No, you don't think of stuff.
-是雪莉說的吧 -才不是呢
- This is Sherry. - No, it isn't.
但如果是她說的 這話也不無道理啊
But if it were, she'd have a point.
是嗎 所以你覺得我很愛控制人嗎
Oh, really? So you think I'm very controlling?
那這榮耀交給你 以后醫生你選
Well, you're welcome to choose the doctors,
修繕工你挑 朋友聚會你來安排
pick the handymen, make plans with friends,
取消聚會你去說吧
cancel plans with friends.
行行行 我懂了
Okay, okay, I get it.
不不不不
No, no, no, no.
你的確是應該多管管事了
You do need to take more control.
而且擇日不如撞日
Actually, from now on,
你的香腸怎么烹調自己來決定吧
you should decide how to cook your own sausage.
行啊 你以為我不會嗎
Fine, you don't think I can do it?
咖啡研磨機 我該怎么做她的獨家醬料
Coffee grinder, how do I make Gloria's special sauce?
現在你不出聲了嗎
Now you're quiet?
杰
Hey, Jay.
-準備好出發了嗎 -去哪
- You ready to go? - Go where?
歌洛莉亞說你會幫忙我
Gloria said you'd help me put in a skylight
給海莉家裝天窗
at Haley's new place.
是的 我吩咐她這么說的
Oh, yeah, I empowered her to say that.
搬家進行得如何
How's the move going?
很好 非常好
So good. Really good.
好得不能再好了
Good, good, good, good.
-那很好啊 -一點都不好
- That's good. - No, it's not.
簡直就是場災難 那屋子太小了
It's a disaster. The place is too small.
所有東西都需要修 我努力保持冷靜 但...
Everything needs fixing. I'm trying to stay calm, but...
他們的屋頂有個洞啊 杰
There's a hole in the ceiling, Jay --
屋頂有洞啊
a hole in the ceiling.
雨水會滴到嬰兒床里
Rain is gonna fall on the crib.
萬一... 萬一有只貓頭鷹
What -- What happens if a -- an owl
叼了個松果飛過時松嘴了呢
picks up a-a pinecone and drops it?
-我的孫兒會被松果砸到啊 -別犯傻了
- My grandchild's gonna get hit with a pinecone! - Don't be silly.
貓頭鷹怎么會叼著松果呢
What would an owl be doing with a pinecone?
最多也就是叼著老鼠或囊地鼠寶寶罷了
At the most, it would be a mouse or a baby gopher.
迪蘭感覺開始靠譜點了
Dylan seems like he's getting his life together,
但他最多也就算是個未知數
but he's still a wild card at best.
我完全懂你現在的感受
I know exactly how you feel.
我想你是真懂 當年你也覺得我是未知數吧
I guess you do. I was your wild card, huh?
我當年沒多少信心
I didn't have a lot of faith.
你那時候耳邊還吊著羽毛之類的吧
Didn't you have feathers hanging off your ear?
-是阻擋惡夢的捕夢網 -那就是我的惡夢
- It was a dream catcher. - It was my nightmare.
我想我懂你要說的意思了
I think I see what you're saying.
我能變得這么棒 沒道理他不行
If I can become awesome, so can Dylan.
我才不是這個意思
That's not what I'm saying.
鬼知道之后會變怎么樣啊
Who the hell knows what's gonna happen?
讓我告訴你人生是怎么回事
Let me tell you something about life.
我們都有覺得自己能掌控人生的錯覺
We all have this illusion that we're in control.
我想去打職業橄欖球
I wanted to play pro football,
結果被人弄得膝蓋不行了
some guy takes my knee out.
我從校園畢業
I graduate from school,
打算騎著摩托穿越全國
I'm gonna drive my motorcycle across the country,
結果被抽簽到去當兵
and some suit pulls my draft number.
我努力工作讓我女兒能讀完大學
I worked my ass off to send my daughter to college,
一個玩雜耍的家伙把她肚子搞大
some juggler knocks her up.
大人 再次跟您道歉
Again, sir, I'm very sorry about that.
我投入無數年心血建立起我的生意
I put in the years, I build my business
好讓自己不用臣服于其他人
so I don't have to answer to anyone,
可現在我還是得歷經磨難
and I still have to jump through hoops
才能換得香腸吃
to get a damn sausage.
最后這部分我聽不懂
You lost me there at that last part.
聽我說 我的意思是
Look, all I'm saying is things
計劃永遠趕不上變化
are always gonna change,
所以你得關關難過關關過
and you have to deal with it.
但好消息是 五年后的這時候
But the good news is, five years from now
當你跟自己的孫兒玩的時候
while you're playing with your grandkid,
今天早就拋到九霄云外了
you won't even remember today.
我還沒有用這個角度想過
I hadn't thought about it like that.
謝謝你 杰
Thanks, Jay.
海莉與迪蘭要搬回來跟我們住了
Huh. Haley and Dylan are gonna have to move back in with us.
沒關系 我受得了
That's okay. I can handle that.
她懷了雙胞胎
She's having twins.
給你來根香腸吧
Let's get you a sausage.
謝謝
Thank you.
那是一箱衣服
It was a box of cloth.
是小帕請她母親給她寄來
Pam asked her mom to ship to her,
三天前寄出的
three days ago.
你演了一出崩潰好戲好留在這里
You faked that break down so you could stay here.
干得漂亮 律師
Well done, counselor.
你看 這就是為什么我寫不出那封信
See! This is why I couldn't write that letter for you.
你對你坑蒙拐騙的事情毫無悔意
You have no remorse for your lying, stealing ways.
但我盯上你了
But I'm on to you.
我會讓你付出代價
And I'm going to make you pay.
你省省吧
No, you ain't.
就你這小身板
You're tiny.
那是我們的臺燈嗎
Hey, hey! Are those our lamps?
小帕
Pam!